월화수목금 계속 일했어
아직 모르는 것 투성이라서
불안이 나를 덮쳐 버려
가끔씩은 기력이 바닥나 버려
월화수목금 계속 일했어
기력이 바닥나도 매일 열심히 하는 수밖에 없잖아
그래도 금요일이 지나면 괜찮아
주말에는 나의 히어로 만나러 가거든
안 돼 더이상은 안 돼 일어 설 수 없어
그런 자신을 바꾸고 싶어 오늘도 가는 거야
언제나 좋은 일만 있는 건 아니야
고통스러워서 울고 싶은 때도 있어
그럴 때는 항상
누구보다 빨리 일어 서는 히어로를 만나고 싶어서
아프지만 달렸어 괴롭지만 달렸어
보답받을 수 있을 지는 모르지만
일단 아직 나는 부러지지 않아
히어로에 나를 겹쳐서
내일도
All days of the week, I go to school
Keeping up with what my friends talk about is actually quite tough for me
What I really like is not yesterday’s TV show
All days of the week, I go to school
I actually don’t even know Shibuya nor Harajuku
But once Friday ends it’ll all be fine
I will go and meet my hero on the weekend
No, there is no way, I can’t even wipe my tears
I want to change myself, so I will go today
I may be laughed by other people for getting anxious over a tiny thing
Without even smiling, he will show me
My hero will teach me, how to run
Although it’s painful and it hurts, I still ran
I don’t know if tomorrow will be any different
But for now, I will not be beaten
With my hero and myself
Even tomorrow
It doesn't always work out
There are tough times that make you want to cry
When that happens
I just want to meet the hero that rises up before anyone
Although it’s painful and it hurts, I still ran
I don’t know if I will be rewarded
But for now, I will not be beaten
With my hero and myself
Even tomorrow
Work, relationships, and education
None of these can be omitted
Just think it’s for your future
Crying is not a bad thing
Encourage yourself from yesterday
And just run earnestly today
He will teach me how to run again
With my hero and myself
Even tomorrow